(Howard:)What now?
(Sheldon:)I have to go to the bathroom.
(Howard:)You just went to the bathroom.
(Sheldon:)I didn't use it because
it didn't seem safe.
(Sheldon:)Despite all my emails,
the toilet didn't have a seatbelt.
(Howard:)Well, it still doesn't.
(Sheldon:)I realize that,
(Sheldon:)but safety concerns went out
the window two apple juices ago.
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)Why are you getting annoyed?
(Howard:)I'm trying to be a better friend,
(Howard:)but you constantly say
and do irritating things.
(Sheldon:)-Like when?
-When?
(Howard:)How about in the car?
I'm an astronaut, and you know it.
(Howard:)You just don't like admitting it,
because you're jealous.
(Sheldon:)Well, truth be told,
(Sheldon:)as a child,
I did dream of going to space.
(Sheldon:)Those astronauts were my heroes.
(Sheldon:)And when you got to go,
it was hard for me.
(Raj:)Thank you.